# Dheerajjha

Sr Backend Developer



Personal Detail

Dheeraj@thedijje.com +918826-810-280 Thedijje.com

Hard skills

PHP Codeigniter

LAMP AWS UX

REST GIT SOL

BASH PWA React

Laravel Docker JS

Soft skills

Leadership

Communication

Project management

Analytical skills

## Conferences

LaravelLive india
PyCon india
ng-India

Eye-sparkling experience in small to big project mostly single handed one, full stack developer with passion for coding, solving real world problem through code & system desgin while keeping business and cost in mind. Believe in thinking twice and code once. Leading LaravelDelhi community, part of PyDelhi, Pycon and LaravelLive.

## Experience

2017 - Current

#### CTE International private limited

- \* Tech lead, handled product and team since inception of idea
- \* Handled system design, project development, server infrastructure and cost management.
- \* Team consist of Backend, iOS, Android developer and front-end developers

2015 - 2017

#### Winculum services/Incisiv.io

- \* Transformed entire multi-site Wordpress based research tool to single app.
- \* Created 10+ tools for customer interaction to leverage research and ROI of business.
- \* Worked more than ever as team despite of being remote work culture.

2015 - 2015

#### Netmaxims Solution/Technologies

- \* Boosted project development by introducing and transforming projects from core PHP to Codeigniter framework.
- \* Removed hassle of Wordpress by creating developer friendly CMS in CI thus moving forward small project by 3x.
- \* Managed projects on Opencart, Wordpress, Woocommerce.

### Education

2010-2014

#### B.Tech in CS from KU - Kurukshetra

- \* Followed passion and changed branch to CS
- \* Spend well time in blogging, learning basic programming.
- \* Made our college's official site with CMS.
- \* Create various micro-sites for college events management and increase student's participation in extra curricular activities.

## Achievements

- \* Zonal winner of NNSC and top 10 in national level
- \* Blog with 2.5M+ hits
- \* Talk at various conferences/Meetups
- \* Volunteering for Pycon, LaravelLive, PyDelhi, LaravelLive Delhi.